okay so I'm gonna show you guys
something well first first we'll go to
the website of what we're trying to
reproduce yes six microseconds of
protein folding so this is a chicken
villian headpiece protein I'm not really
sure what it does maybe we should we
should look into that but look at this
so they have a simulator and they start
with the protein unfolded so I'm not
even sure how you how you get a protein
unfolded we're gonna look into that
we've been learning a lot of biology
we've been learning about amino acids
I've been reading molecular biology of
the cell sixth edition it tells you many
good things you learn all about proteins
you learn about the different amino
acids I know what a peptide bond is
right now I know what a sidechain is
yeah you got to know these things
amino acids have an amino and it called
box'll so let's take a look here yeah
yeah you can see this is this is four
amino acids put together you start with
a met you know because that's that's the
start codon and then you have these
peptide bonds which this is the amino
side and this is the carboxyl side see
that he fits in the side chains are
alternating from side to side but that's
not really true you can actually rotate
this stuff however you want please turn
up Mike you can turn the mic up let make
sure we got the right Mike
first of all here we got the first mic
yeah you guys know I'm part time to come
I know I will take we'll take half a
second to shelf or comma not to be
confused with this comment hey I this
comment a I we are now a profitable
company so that's very exciting
okay I renewed or I went up as well true
profitability guys wow it's a really
good feeling yeah and I'm done with my
I'm done with my four years of testing
so it's pretty nice because I mean what
exactly do you do right um it's
interesting I've been looking at all
these startups doing layoffs and you
know it's its last in first out so the
people who got just recently got hired
are the first ones to get fired but you
know basically all you're left with at
that point is you're gonna be left with
executives and middle managers I think
these companies are firing the people
who did the real work and now you're
gonna have well executives and middle
managers so we at common we do it
differently I think both executives and
middle managers is stupid everybody had
come as an engineer so yeah now come
about by oh we're gonna fall proteins
um startup employees are more risk than
the founder well if you have a founder
that takes less risk than your startup
employees you're a start-up that's
that's practically criminal you know I
see I see these startups I see these
founders who take VC money and they pay
themselves $400,000 salaries it's
disgusting it's really it's really
disgusting so I buy my celery , $78,000
cob and that's the highest that ever was
was 80 you can't do that you can't if
you as a founder are taking less risk
than your startup employees there's
something seriously wrong with your
company yeah so know as a start-up
employee
you should definitely have have less
risk than a founder you should be you
should be paid a higher salary the so
again a lot of startups can with this
right so a lot of they'll put
restrictions on employee equity and you
know a lot of times employees don't even
really know about this so at comments
the other way around the restrictions
are on transfer of my equity not
transfer of any employee equity
I'm muted I don't think I'm muted
so yeah if you're at a startup where the
founders are taking less risks and the
employees your your scammers
I mean they're scammers a lot of the VCS
are scammers to remember that VCS don't
actually produce any value it's not
their money that they're investing the
VCS just scam LPS the LPS a lot of times
don't care like the Louisiana pension
fund you know get the Louisiana pension
fund isn't being managed by the cops and
firefighters who will pay out the
Louisiana pension funds of course being
managed by corrupt politicians who I'm
sure line their pockets when the pension
fund goes up and when the pension fund
goes down oh hey hey you fought fires
and not in the suburbs for 30 years but
now sorry they took your pension fund
and they invested it and we work I'm
sorry um what would you ask founders
what their take-home salary is I think
founders should be paid the lowest of
any employee of this job if you're gonna
found a company and you're not doing it
and you're not looking for the upside
later on of course the upside to
founders is they do get a much larger
share of the equity of the company so
the upside on that and that size is much
larger right but the risk is much larger
I you want higher upside take high risk
right what do we do when we do comm
niboshi ations
you get a choice you get a choice
between well like usually it's three
tiers you want like more salary or you
want you want salary equity or you want
say are ya buddy
you can choose so what's the highest the
average founder should make and an onion
prop well yeah I mean in an unprofitable
company you shouldn't be paying above
should actually probably be paying below
market rate
well no I mean look look right now
you're seeing with all of these large
companies you're seeing you're seeing
the multi bailed out by the government
when they just spent the last two years
doing stock buybacks and making their
executives right right so where's that
money coming back from the executives
into the business now of course that
doesn't exist right yeah I mean our
stock how was this how's this legal how
are we letting I had a way as a country
let this happen
time to start fixing things voice time
to stuff fix a place I know OBS is being
shown I have to say screamed what would
I be doing or , doesn't won't work I
don't I have money
you know why I have money because I
don't buy anything
I don't really spend money of anything
so if you don't really spend money on
anything you have money it's cool no
have the boss I do get paid the least
and comma yet
yeah if you're a founder of a start-up
you should be paying getting paid the
same as how much driving or a seventy
eight thousand dollars a year
you should spend on financial advisors
and lawyers and do an IPO that
so if you want to take a company public
so an IPO is is done through investment
banks usually the way that you do an IPO
is you get an investment bank to agree
to purchase a certain amount of your
shares I never want those kind of people
the investment bank kind of people
anywhere near any company I have is
taken now you have some other options
you could do DPOs but if you still want
to get listed on a major exchange you're
gonna have to do the same the same s1
rigmarole you're giving basically
control of your company off and you may
not want to do that um so if you do want
to go public for did it be able to go to
the event there is a bunch of cleaner
ways to do it I think and I think
they're gonna become more obvious sure
we have the 2017 crypto ico scam phase
but it kind of led a genie out of the
bottle that isn't going to be put back
in I think that it's going to become
much cheaper for companies to
effectively sell their shares to the
public and you see things trending this
way you see like you see reggae you see
the JOBS Act and yeah like ideally I
mean my dream you know I don't want to
violate any laws but my dream would just
be to turn every chef comment to a token
in 20 our c20 token and then it can
trade on whatever exchanges if you don't
think 78 K is a lot and you're
privileged as well so 78 K is less than
anybody else could nobody gets faith our
starting salaries are 80
Antti CEO alright just just just bliss
we've been been on a rant we're gonna
take a look oh it's a TED talk oh oh oh
I'm disgusted already anti CEO playbook
that provocative that prioritizes people
over profits no no profits are a good
thing profits if you have a company
that's profitable the way that you make
a company profitable is you provide a
good or a service to other people
voluntarily right a profitable company
is good an unprofitable company is bad
when you have a company that takes
investment money and then pays the
founders $400,000 salaries that's bad
because that's not benefiting anybody
that's just benefiting people for being
connected what do you mean by people
should come over profits alright
whenever I see arguments like that I see
I see the same thing on the other side
right I see oh we need to you know
everybody needs a living wage well I
mean it says who right everybody should
be paid fairly for the value they can
provide and create but that's like what
the doesn't that like make obvious sense
oh we have
you're paid based on how easy you are to
be replaced yeah I don't know I'm
generally I'm generally anti TEDTalk um
and I'm anti TEDTalk because a lot of
TED Talks instead of actually giving you
any real information there's real
information and then there is something
that like lights up the party a brain
that says you're getting information
right news does this too and it's the
presentation style of TED Talks they're
so overly blankets and when I say these
things words will appear on the screen
right and you use this almost fake
profound accent yeah people should be
pay for the value and if a company's not
profitable how I've won woo let's get on
the hype train a TED talks are fake
enlightenment what do I make of a zoom
situation I don't know anything about
this is oom situation it's nice to be
beyond the hype train don't you deserve
more than your employees just because
you're so productive oh yeah I mean how
productive am i but I do have more
equity than then everyone who works at
calm I have the most equity first and
you know you get you get more equity
than else but if you know on the flip
side of that you take the most risk
right I didn't learn this until really
kind of it was too late but what you're
really giving the VCS in exchange for
the money is social capital um VC is
just a way of turning social capital
into dollars I don't know I mean yeah
given the alternatives it might be a
decent way to to to fund companies but
it's uh it's it's
mushiya ng the results that it's
produced especially recently I think we
can find better ways you can't buy
common stock common is a private company
and we're not selling if I'm not rich
where I still pay myself seventy eight
thousand dollars yeah I don't I mean I
don't spend more than seventy eight
thousand dollars a year I'm that's
that's about that's about breakeven for
me and I'm spending money on things that
like I've paid this apartment I don't
really have to pay for this apartment no
equity so equity can matter in a bunch
of ways without a company going public
so you can pay dividends dividends are
an option not to be confused with stock
buybacks very different
you can potentially sell your equity on
a on a private market you can you can go
public or you can get acquired is there
a reason I why would I want to be CEO
what do you think CEO was do
why don't I need to pay for the
apartment I do I do pay for the
apartment I don't have to I could go
live somewhere cheaper
all right time to start doing I wouldn't
live in a cardboard box but I don't know
I mean uh it'd kind of be nice little
roommates again I like living two mates
for the most part I got this cuz I
wanted to focus on a comma being
profitable and uh yeah I moved here
about ten months ago and we had our
first profitable quarter
okay so this is a chicken villian
headpiece protein I think I spelled it
right
yeah villain I let's look up what
villainous we have some some context the
tissue-specific actin binding protein
associated with the actin core bundle of
the brush border this is gonna be a big
Wikipedia rabbit all proteins that bind
to active actin is a family of globular
multifunctional proteins that form
microfilaments that become part of the
cytoskeleton hey what's a brush border
micro valise
Oh the helix domain of the headpiece
ours is a little bit smaller than that
made up of seven domains Wow
supervillain okay well that's what
they'll it is so I've already got it
here I downloaded the protein PDB and
actually committed it last night in
preparation for this stream so we can
get the visualizer up here load up the
party so this is what it looks like but
this is what it looks like already
folded when you download it from the
protein database it already comes folded
so if we don't want it fold it what
we're gonna have to do is we're just
gonna get the well actually you know
what let's just use our translator and
let's get it from DNA
what
or genomic coordinates
so I did find that if I go in my
proteins villain and then I load it up
we can get the amino acids right here so
I could just use them from this mat
loser-ass blue asked fee ideally no what
we want to do is we want to build a
framework so we've already done remember
um translation on SR transcription turns
RNA into proteins but it doesn't turn it
into proteins it just turns it into a
strand of amino acids in order to turn
those amino acids into proteins we're
gonna have to fold them that doesn't
look useful and in order to fold them
we're going to need a well I mean that's
you know a hard problem but I think we
can do it with a molecular dynamics
simulator oh here we go here's something
it's too long okay we'll just use this
you just copied it here wait there's two
Mets in here how can you have two Mets
though you can have more start codons as
long as you don't a stop codon oh I see
I get it
that's Google this and see what we got
[Music]
go to Jean Vito Wow what's this
then chromosome to the chicken
chromosome tell
Wow
the zoom level is high enough zoom in Oh
now are there a Lulu Sox
sequence name for protein view
oh it's part of this big protein
[Music]
Oh faster sequence Oh I think this is
what I want okay I'll take it stick it
in the feeling directory other faster
sequences and did I stick txt at the end
of it okay so this is actually already
after it's been translated into amino
acids and they use the letters as
desired this
today oh yeah look at this great is that
36 this is 36 amino acid protein okay so
this and this are the same thing the
only difference is this one is already
folded so I mean we can probably check
that mat blue sir no whatever D is is
gonna be next
Oh ask what it shouldn't be asked is it
different
they wouldn't wait Matt looser ass
glue ass oh is it possible that D is ass
D is an ass I get it
oh that's funny okay so now we're gonna
have to write something which turns
FASTA into protein
this might already exist now of course
it's not actually gonna fold the protein
for me oh no I don't
the amino acid system cannot be
translated into a structure that easily
yeah I know why you don't think that but
PBB format is not sequence it is
structure you must have your structure
experimentally solve or have your
structure predicted by I passer so I
looked into what I passer was a little
bit by the way if you guys want
something to follow along with how I've
been thinking about this this is how
I've been doing this
I'm not going to the New York Times's
github in a rate of threading assembly
refinement yeah when you read this like
it first generates first identify
structural templates on the PDB by
multiple thread and approach romance
then it goes through bio lip so I Tasker
seems to be this like incredibly complex
I mean I guess we can just see what
happens
oh no I have to give them an email
that's too much effort but this still
isn't what I want I want to put this in
a line okay so this is the structure and
you have your mets and your stuffs the
thing is we don't care let's just try
something
see this works
PDB file is for open an app for pi Josh
look it's a nephew Nunez who likes the
matheno name now the problem is they
knew exactly how far apart to put all
these things I don't really know how far
apart to put them so we're gonna try and
experiment here or do it science boys
we have a limb champion integrator sub
positions
minimize energy hold set positions on it
context that the wrong number of
positions because I didn't reinitialize
the system
no template found for residue one met
number of atoms is similar but it's
missing six atoms no well let's try to
figure out why it's missing six apps I
mean it sure looks like it has a lot of
atoms to me don't you all think let's
just get the add hydrogen sup that's
with respect to the force field so we're
gonna need a force field so we can use
amber or we can use charm they're both
high quality no template found for
residue one met the set of atoms matches
in mint but the bonds are different but
it worked okay when they loaded it the
other way alright this is probably still
just complaining because I don't have to
do I need the end a carboxylic group on
there I don't think the term matters at
all
no template found for a residue one met
a set of an atom's matches and met but
the bonds are different we got a long
way to go boys got a long way to go all
right let's figure out what this P DV
format is first let's look at a mat
where's the mat mat Sione's so we have
an N I don't know if we have those H's 1
2 3 4 5 5 carbons
that's a carven two three four five
carbons okay that seems right we have
one oxygen you have one sulfur oh we
only have one oxygen do we have two
oxygens oh we only have one oxygen okay
well my methionine needs more oxygen
there'd be given an oxd that fixes it
let's see what this looks like oh who
put that oxygen all the way out there
that was a stupid place to put the
oxygen no template found for residue one
met it means your input topology okay so
we can look at the amber 99 we're using
amber 99 SP now we want to make Metz not
a seam at just a met
oh this is interesting okay I'll get rid
of that just I think that was wrong the
set of atoms matches nment
but the bonds are different oh there's
an external bond I see that's an end of
it it has an external body I'm 17 Arcee
meds and Mets be like does it mean like
a starting net and how come that's not a
seam at
oh I kind of think you can't have okay
fine fine fine I'll have a met Anna Lou
I think this you can't just sit
complains if you have a one amino acid I
think the starting ones are special so
oh look we have a met Anna Lou now
that's a fancy looking protein what do
you think of my two amino acid protein
atoms match Lou but the bonds are
different perhaps the chain is missing a
terminal okay so that seems wrong eat
well wait there's C and there's n oh I
think that's actually a thing see what
am I thinking off there's the 5 end and
the 3 end I know that C looks like the
end because it has an oxd let's just
take a look in my bio textbook here yeah
that Theo knees don't have a oxd but if
I put a oxd at the end of my uh my fingy
that seems good all right so let's get
my ox down I just stuck it there
Oh should I stick it there as well so I
stick it above the hydrogen's I also
need a cz is that only at the end put it
on Istanbul ooh let's see if that fixes
it
yeah of course my ox is gonna be a
stupid place look at that oxygen all the
way out there that's so far away from
everything else
oh yeah body right now let's try it
let's run the simulation for a few steps
and what we're gonna see is does the
just that oxygen like stay far away or
does it come back okay wow I really got
that lunge Abbi and integrate or turned
up let's turn it down a little bit
potential energy lots of kids Ulis
alright
whoa hey look the oxygen came back
I wonder if minimize it oh no probably
just didn't even save the first step
let's save every step and let's just go
for ten steps look the oxygen came back
was the oxd yeah look at that ox look it
came back wait that's a weird place to
put it get both attached to that same
carbon maybe on a loo here's a little oh
yeah yeah they both go on the tarp
carboxyl terminus Wow
remember how I put it in a stupid place
and then it showed up here oh that's
nice let's get rid of the minimize
energy and see if that was always
actually doing it oh look it crashed oh
yeah that oxygen went flying but if we
first minimize energy okay so let's try
something else now and actually it'd be
nice because I think we could just do
this on the protein if this works but
take my model of positions and they're
like positions oh that's nice wow this
might be it this might be a short stream
thank you for the subscriptions we
overflowed honestly guys you know what I
would do if I was on the coronavirus
task force I wouldn't want to be the
front face I wouldn't want to be the guy
I wouldn't want to be the guy telling
people about the plant but you all know
what the plan should be it's not great
let's see model or depositions does
shape list says no attribute shapes of
course must a little bunch of each shape
land in the model are dot position so
we're gonna try putting them all at 0 0
0 let's see what happens say 4x and just
the same
particle coordinate is NaN well that's
sad don't make it man oh and part of the
problem I'd have to do with the fact
that I didn't tell it my was
nanometers but me doesn't matter I don't
know looks kind of similar to that whiny
value equals zero position no yeah now
we're talking particle coordinate is NaN
[Music]
okay if it just doesn't like them all
being on top of each other random dot
random
oh sweet look at that it becomes a
protein II again yeah yeah let's see if
they go to different confirmations haha
so exciting so exciting this is so
exciting ok let's try
wait I want to don't wait to the save 20
steps oh I did save 20 steps just
nothing happened
let's try a little bit more I wait for
it to warm up a little bit got to warm
up my protein a little warming up a
little bit more than that warm up my
protein got to make it nice and warm
that's a quality looking protein alright
wait so let's just try it I mean this
unfolded thing is stupid I don't
actually need that let's just take the
protein PDB and then we'll do 0
positions on it I don't see what ya know
it's nan-oh
oh it's only now it's we're stepping
it's not step so watch my step 20
whoa it's my protein but it's all
unfolded like that no no I think that
looks pretty good look at that it's a
randomly folded chicken head piece villa
head piece or whatever whatever's all
right let's save a few more steps and
let's see if we can do that without it
going down it goes man just like
crapping machine learning models alright
let's see my protein falls folding
folding and folding arts folding way too
slowly I don't have that kind of
patience fold faster
folding folding folding Oh is it not
warm enough what temperature does
chicken headpiece fall down oh look at
that look at that potential energy going
down that means my shits folding folding
folding folding oh no this is fun oh
we're folding all right just to prove
that we didn't cheat at all let me just
write the thing that actually like
creates that file you know that creates
that unfolded file
there's otherwise like we don't know
informations could be leaking but we
want to turn amino acid sequences into
proteins that we fault hey it's cupcake
thank you for subscribing we got a lot
of people in here y'all like folding
alright so I think we're pretty soon
where we're gonna just need to throw a
lot of computation at this we might
already be at that point hmm folding and
folding folding let's go 50 here let's
go 30 thousand let's see what happens
oh this is a long thing for my folding
go is my falling
folding folding all right well we should
figure out how long we expect to have to
do this for before it falls I'll look at
it trying to fold all right really it
wants to fall boys it wants to fold we
can open up the combo GPU cluster we can
do that we have these options available
to us folding folding oh look at that
protein what's a beautiful protein I
mean it's not yeah
is it gonna start to form its alpha
helix ease I learned about these by
reading a bio textbook mMmmm okay let's
work out how many steps we should have
to simulate it for so I've heard that
this thing folds in 5 microseconds bill
in a head piece folding and time 4 to 5
microseconds okay so let's say 5
microseconds divided by that much Pico
seconds what that's not what I want I
want you to give me a number and that's
stupid I cancelled out to set up and I
put the parentheses there we go okay so
what I mean we're all 5 we're off by a
couple you know orders of magnitude here
that's how many steps we got to do
that's a lot of steps 250 how many more
steps is that than what we already did
Wow proteins take a long time to fall
boys we knew this though we knew this
though and we should be prepared for it
yeah I'm folding on my GPU right now oh
no it went man
where is negative potential energy good
Oh No
we're not
alright I think it's too big in that
doesn't say
too long this time the initialization is
totally different
these are in a totally different range
more negative means deeper in the
potential well is that what we want to
be or where we don't want to be we can
check in a minute what might folded
protein has oh yeah that doesn't look
good okay it's not even connected look
at that wow that's really shitty that's
the worst initialization I've seen in a
long time who broke my proteins alright
let's try something we should also
figure out if the amber SV is a good
forcefield or not or if we should try a
different voice field first let's see
what I what happens when I put my
already folded protein oh wow that's a
lot of negative energy you know so
negative energies is good wiggle wiggle
wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle
I also I scaled up my my thingy here cuz
I kind of think what happened does the
thing you got caught on itself well that
looks pretty good
those are the right order of magnitude
when they have the ones that were like
10,000 it was doing badly and I think we
want to see this go down right folding
folding oh look its folding so good look
this used to be crappier and now it's
folding better holding okay I think
we're gonna have to fold it for that
many times more though which isn't great
or maybe we can just do less picoseconds
here how many picoseconds can I make my
Langevin integrator and have it still
work hmmm look at it it's trying to fold
it's trying to fold boys
max to femtoseconds oh no I'm already at
the Marik's got to throw second that's
not many seconds at all
damn electrodynamics is hard no I say
all right first thing before we're gonna
figure out how to make our foldings go
faster how long did that take
what kind of Python time it right the
important time
well this is folding we can break the
thingy to parse this well first off do I
want to use amber or do I want to use
some other one I have an idea some of
them are faster than others too
it's not straightforward to say which
one is best
I hate when that's true I'll look at
those big negative numbers all this has
to be a good one I think it almost
folded even if it's long you should
write your own
[Music]
okay we can't just watch the proteins
not fault let's go back to pasta and yes
oh yeah we were figuring out which force
field there was a one of those papers
that I posted last night talked about
they had a paper with a folded proteins
correctly let's just figure out which
force field they used talking about any
issues
a flurry of forcefield related
development here
when folding simulations with a diverse
typology
these proteins they folded them that's
so cool
which force field they use Wow and then
didn't work for Nagato
pairwise variants of the generalized
born model
Wow cardi B knows about this
[Music]
first District
yeah and go to the Bronx man you stay in
Manhattan Brooklyn go to Queens you only
go to Staten Island if you're going to
Brooklyn and you're gonna cross the
goggles in the Verrazano and I think one
guy went to the Bronx once but it was
just to go to the zoo no okay well I
don't think that's what they meant by
GBM v2 oh here we go
ffs oh there's an amber okay I think I'm
using that amber oh performance is good
oh that sounds sweet okay then this
force field sounds good enough we can
use it
this was 2009 they haven't made better
ones yet
[Music]
the mini Dom objects not colorful Oh
mini diamond dog park oh cool
I was excited about our amber yeah we
got beautiful
these are the atom type so they have
masses that's cool charges out of time
so I use a mini Dom documents get
elements by tag name I'll note a yeah
that's my force field about child notes
okay
residues these are atom types
okay they're residues Margie can I just
say get elements by tag name resident
perfect okay so the residues are the
different different shits okay what do I
do with a Dom element residue that's
what they call amino acids
okay get on with my tag name Wow Wow
okay guys we can get the atoms how do I
get the name of the residue our equals
is it attributes name yes it is actually
it's me I'm valiant perfect ace all
right we do have to turn those letters
into those thingies for our in residues
okay we're gonna have to turn these
fastest letters into these but I think
we can just
we're gonna have to turn these into
these how do I do that and I could type
it in but I do hate typing
no that one highlighted so much nicer
than that one whatever all right wants
to have fun w it it's gonna be faster
than the other choice wasn't too bad
all right who wants to see some magic
thanks if I could do this LP got split
on that and then we want to say don't be
equals dick zip LP 1 foot 2 0 1 2 LP
hope he's not defined we've got a lot of
data processing Bruce
[Music]
what are those things calls we'll just
call them LTL or letter a three-letter
all right so now we should add this all
to the library actually let's call it to
writing it in here for now okay
so we have the Adams
then we have our fastest it's all right
so who's ready to do this for a a
because it's an amino acid FASTA we want
to go LTL AAA
we probably want to go operon that okay
now these should all be in Adams Keys
gonna have to be a little careful
because the last one we're gonna have to
go an ox on but this should be okay DL
oh yeah beautiful too bad they're all
shitty Dom elements let's take a look at
a mat for now hey Dom elements you know
let's figure out what we actually need
from this does not have childhoods okay
what doesn't Adam have and Adam has a
name and a type okay actually all we
really need is the name so we can just
say I did before tonight attribute song
yeah there we go yeah that's so now
all right um get elements by tag name so
we actually want to say X dot attributed
a without borax and you know I may be
terrible at bio but when you all see me
do data parsing right yeah that data
parson Lana's got a blue checkmark oh
yeah she's more famous than me I'm gonna
be a riot soon though I think that might
be my right and right go through yet my
friend invited me Araya oh wow I've
heard I'm gonna hate Raya so is that all
right so we got a lot of those thingies
what kind of in jail who's new here
who's being disrespectful Emile Raya
don't be disrespectful this is all about
respect channel we like respect let's
look at the villain not the Ubik you
know I'm not too keen
let's take a look here all right we're
gonna have to figure out what all these
little shits are what's this little
what's that little it's always
added then when they separated by these
tabs you know they're just spaces that's
weird
how do I know how many spaces maybe I
can use oh here bio PBB PBB parser
can I write pdb files
dice just looks kind of more complicated
biyo PDV might be exactly what you want
and then again it might not
why do they have a separate biopython
things very good atom of this atom
contains describes that alpha and atom
as the first residue which is a proline
residue residue residue residue what to
do all those are in angstroms they're
not in nanometers
I know it's a residue mine idiot the
next three columns are the occupancy
temperature factor how do I get those
what's a temperature factor
well the occupancies always one that's
easy
you know crap we've know what type the
atomists that always the first looks
like it's always the first letter
what's the temperature factor wait who's
saying someone else is acting like a
douchebag
no no your band you got a time out be
nice to people here
if you know why we're gonna make you
choose yellow cheddar cheese does
referred with this dinner so I'm not
sure if I'm allowed to eat it
you're telling them about the vaccine
all right all right
no spreading misinformation pink we know
let's see you later
the ATL do things it works we have to
figure out what the temperature factors
we know oh the uncertainty of this Adams
position do the temperature that doesn't
matter
[Music]
yeah buddy
all right remember to follow a subscribe
boy Sandra Elsie does these are the
people I like in my channel we got to
subscribe because we don't subscribe why
should I keep doing this I only do it
for the money now we do it for the
learning and we bring you guys because
occasionally some of you say intelligent
days
you need the topology bro bro I actually
don't need the topology because we're
gonna fold it with a folding make sure
to load the correct topology file name
oh that's fine I don't care
I understand why you thought you think I
need the Penta that the apology but I do
that one wait a second how did this work
before then when I start just a one
amino acid in and and did something I
don't know whatever we'll get to that
crap later let's for now just try this
this is kind of a messy file you know
just index out of range
the amount of spaces could actually
matter Oh God
okay fine how many spaces is that spaces
for the next one Oh what about when it's
like that how to do that looks more like
columns misaligned residue named great
miss wine to me oh it wants another
space there
what is it Matt cuz the h DS is that
what it's mad about like I have to like
put them stupidly like that I don't even
know how to do that okay do not do that
never mind fine I'll do it I'll do it
yeah eh
[Music]
there's last of all it's a space in
front of that that's not work well
because I'm doing minus 4 or something
[Music]
tamson here
okay it's still slightly wrong I think
we do want the minus 4 yeah - 4 is
correct ok now my thing you look stupid
like that - does it load now misaligned
residue name
who knows how to fold I'm listening
bro this is my pdb socks yeah i agree
that pdb socks alright well I don't know
let's just compare my atoms to these
atoms and say exactly what's different
I'll just make it match perfectly
oh well as you can see mine is a line
one off of theirs so if you change that
7 to a 6
yeah who could not convert string to
float oh look at that
oh no okay okay we're learning we're
learning we're learning
okay well that's good to know so 38 take
my work
driving research before I do this one
you're gonna have to change these let's
just do it right 5.3 F
I'm sorry 28.3 f might still be wrong
because we might want them against each
other this is the worst file format ever
and whoever did this should really be
you know you did this and why like like
right here this file format just showing
me that there's a lot of room for you
know someone to come in who knows things
about computers to come disrupt this
space I don't think about computers
character rid of my spaces
okay we're gonna need another space
before that we need another one point
two spaces 1.00 and then a lot of space
isn't straight did I get my lot of
spaces right my lot of oh yeah look at
that oh what a good quality format that
was all perfect okay it loads let's see
does that even work
oh yeah but aside from the fact that
there's nothing there
it works great oh now I think my model
is gonna complain when I try to add
hydrogen's zero zero can't be raised to
a negative power a so not like zero
that's just a random
the atoms match fee but all right we're
gonna need to shove an office to the end
of this why are we only up two feet is
there another seat does it feel like we
got don't get cool like that has an
August and mind is not even tossed how'd
they get more atoms than me no I don't
think their atoms started at one no
template found bonds are different press
the chains missing a terminal dude
that's true okay just say
how long did I cook my macaronis for is
it too long right into the wall
someone who's gonna wait to go home and
time this and finds life looks good for
like twice as long as I sure
[Music]
we do anarchist on the end of that
that's pretty good for those guys at
home who are following I'll show you
what a ops dis cuz I've been learning
bio
this guy here or the one with the single
bond is in August alright now we've had
an August does it load it lows of course
we still can't look at it this just work
if I do that particle position is mad
okay it has a few nano shoes Oh random
not random actually isn't what I want I
want random guy random -
[Music]
we still can't see anything but that's
okay I'm sorry this is a mess cool
okay we got our protein back I don't
know why it has so much potential energy
one of the form all types of the time at
our DBMS well you gotta have atomicity
compliance integrity and data isn't out
what the asset model for database is
this I don't know I learned that once so
now you have a step to wait some of this
crap that we don't need do not need that
this belongs up here we do not need this
don't need that and we don't need that
right unfolded is good-looking I'll
commit right and folder once it works
10,000 steps go there loads it up adds
the hydrogens then we can look at it no
no we don't want to look at temp
unfolded we want to look at tenth output
and also where did I get foster from
it's a little unfair okay I love doing
science oh yeah
let's let it fall for a bad secret yeah
no don't scare up stalking local members
this is nature and it gets stuck in
local mins then so does nature a GPU in
a minute
now build a simple boy oh what's next I
don't know that's for the next stream if
this stream we manage to fold a villain
that's a great victory okay it's doing
something now I have GPU in a map look
OpenCL Bob Mathews of GPUs I just don't
have NVIDIA GPUs because of apples beef
within video I'm good actually goes back
to the job I think Steve Jobs got pissed
that like Nvidia did a bad job soldering
their GPUs or like the soldering
recommendation they gave Apple was wrong
and they were broken MacBooks and like
Nvidia didn't pay for it
and Jobs was like I would never using
Nvidia again see look we go look at the
atoms - yeah I'll use Jupiter epoxy is
one of these days you think I missed
file-naming 100 you're right I did no
you're right all right that's a bug in
my library good couch
see this is why we have streamers this
is why we do it live
Little Miss bunk OpenCL is gonna get
depreciated we'll see what happens
I'll believe it when I see it I don't
know then Jenna I think what Apple
depreciates things it's usually good for
the industry okay so we worked out how
much do we have to do how we have to do
so many steps so I wrote this last night
and this is just fold so we'll do
writing from scratch here
usury this is already committed no
template found the residue group met I
don't understand this is literally the
same thing that I was doing before right
what changed
[Music]
which is actually giving me that command
under forcefield create system why do I
have to add the hydrogens for something
try adding some hydrogen
choose better I cool I forgot some
hydrogen's there right look at that
going down
[Music]
how many outputs do I walk sad wat 100 I
want 100 then we put steps divided by
we're in our cars so this can actually
[Music]
let's FaceTime did Bill Gates y'all
penny was Bill it's it's not viable
FaceTime a minute I'm sold
mmm what's the water model being used so
I mean it's a good question
I think this is the water model but I
didn't actually add solvent we could try
to add solvent and see what happens the
options the last time you complained
about being charged but right so that
was the folding job we just did
[Music]
can I do a thousand here does it still
work - in Celsius is right 27 is 273
Kelvin to zero Celsius
look at it fold what's going down
it didn't get faster I just printed out
more stuff okay 1000 works alright who's
ready to push this to a GPU okay so this
computer has you GPUs in it and only
have it has a Titan V so that's a nice
GPU right Titan be nice to peel all
right we have big fold let's fold the
visible devices equal zero
let's see how fast that is faster
oh so fast now who does
[Music]
let's go
it's probably a little too much let's
first try
let's boss
[Music]
yeah so it's gonna fold for thousands of
those steps well that's gonna take a
long time can I look at the output in
the meantime probably wow it's really
going all over the place
[Music]
my protein is holding pity Cudas now
that's just my desktop at work this is
what a cluster yeah I don't know how
I'll open mmm work with multiple GPUs
but we can try bro max as well go back
to the Miller option let's see we go max
open mmm
well how old ask GPUs are these go Mac
CPU vs. GPU
no don't use named whatever you do does
anybody use open mm or is it just too
slow
we're folding would say did it fall
[Music]
yeah no more no false information we all
spread false information around here
people getting bad left and right on the
internet for spreading false information
you know Oh fun fact
remember how I denied all like of the
conspiracy theories oh yeah I definitely
did I the conspiracy theories that it's
like some bioweapon attack but um this
is real so yeah
Corona may have two hundred million
atoms thankful to get us two hundred
million atoms Corona has 30k base pairs
so like 10k amino acids and then like
every amino acid has on average like ten
atoms just like a hundred thousand atoms
those are lower numbers it seems like
it's doing something maybe
look it's like trying to fold guys it
wants the fault it's like I'm a protein
and I want to fold if this is a problem
with my solvent or my force field
I'm never gonna fix it
no no 20 to 30 items for protein that's
probably more right the whole virus is
like 10,000 amino acids so it's like 200
so you're off by a factor a thousand
there see what there's looked like six
microseconds wow that's so many
microseconds
yeah look it flops around and does
nothing in theirs as well for a while
yeah look at it flop around do nothing
for a while then it gets better
oh man if we see some coils appear or
how exciting lap e is actually using the
whole GPU or is that using like a tiny
amount of it okay using my whole GPU 99%
that's pretty good I mean it's only
using 59 watts which I don't exactly
understand I also have computers with a
GPU don't know if that's better oh look
it's going down the energy landscape oh
that's cool
up up it's sucking that local minimum
whoa well that's a cool video that's
where my protein is right now just
wiggling out there but then I think
what's my ratted on the thing it didn't
show that it had less potential energy
our goal is don't care my simulator
knows this so I don't have to - what -
very
look the numbers are going down how
these numbers are way lower than you
used to be
stupidly wiggle around for a while
oh that was almost that was almost a
helix thingy no that's a lie I wasn't
most a helix thing
it's game sucks
okay let's
already that crap anymore dd-did delete
it I have to like click outside up
yeah like I don't get it so this is the
folded protein how does the folded
protein have like the same potential
energy as mine mine actually is lower
potential energy
if it is folded though it does pretty
much seem to stay folded well actually I
don't know doesn't even look like it's
really staying folded let's improve the
code
you
factor of a hundred and that too
sixteen minutes 16 times 100 minutes
okay I don't fold in a day
it sounds pretty nice
you
okay well this is the one chance we had
to look at this protein not fold itself
despite massive amounts of computes
being poured into making it fold did
this one unfold weight and also did I
write scratch I did not write scratch
it's my own fault now it seems like once
it's folding it's pretty stable it's a
little Wiggly there but now it's a safe
I do wonder what happens if I open the
temperature wait a second do I need to
make it warmer
they used amber and they use a
generalized born salvation model how did
they do it in 200 nanoseconds that's so
fast
holding free energy at 300 calories
hmm
I use born one what am I looking at Oh
open mmm supports all the generalized
born models used by Amer
ss all three
and the road three
creating a system for a print top file
what's a prim top file oh I turned off
my non-bonded interactions
I don't know if that matters
boys
how's this protein doing in the not
unfolding department
it does not unfold
Micron's bus crash
all right who knows why my protein don't
fault
should we try to fold the corona protein
he had at Corona protein didn't weigh
the membrane protein I was looking at
that's the one I wanted to fall last
time
he's our tool which is the shortest
translated and the low protein it's
pretty short
a little bit right now let's try in
Corona viola first let's see quickly of
my thingy Wiggles around enough well
that's more atoms and stuff so this is a
coronavirus envelope protein let's even
Falls particle position is NaN try again
is there any way to mess with
temperature in a dynamic way I could
particle position is Ned well that sucks
[Music]
let's try not many steps what if I do
want
division by zero because writing in
these are steps your initial conditions
suck bro well yeah I mean that's
how do you want me to change them unless
you're saying you want me to cheat but
you know I'm not a cheater man can't we
can't already say how the proteins fold
it that's just cheating and any anyone
can cheat how is my big protein folding
going start with a linear chain of amino
acids bro you didn't like that I put
them all right all right we could make
it more linear will that upset you last
you don't like that I just shoved
everything randomly alright we'll start
with a linear chain to be fair the other
guys started with a linear chain I'll
write linear chain bro
how many angstroms apart are they
alright alright alright you want it neat
I should try folding the original yeah
the original one works I mean why you
just want me to set
alright alright well stretch this will
stretch it out can I put it in some
solvent to get proteins to stretch out
automatically can I do that
alright you all didn't like my random
[Music]
you gotta lower the temperature but
solvent this implicit bro
alright I got you I got you I got you
alright we got a flat and analysis of
paper and origami alright alright
alright because it's flat it out alright
good I like the direction we're going
here guys are doing some good thinking
alright because the game you're right
this protein doesn't look like it wants
to fall right well at least it's true
that the other guys definitely had a
flat protein and I don't have a flat
protein so that's definitely a
difference between me and them and we
know that their thingy kind of worked so
you know Oh sad face okay click here dee
dee nice
I like your shortcut key bro I like
shortcut key beau okay well now there's
nothing here because everything's
terrible alright let's just find let's
just start with an M no actually I can't
just have an M I need an M plus
something else cuz by just having an
it's gonna give me crap about how you
can't put the oxd on the last thingy or
else angry alright I'll try an ml that
sounds nice okay okay alright
I like that it showed up pretty nice
stick a lot last night yeah all my atoms
are just everywhere okay okay okay okay
okay you can escape DeeDee I can escape
DeeDee
if I'm already o escape DeeDee alright
alright I like this I ain't ya know
bonds well yeah I don't know I mean I
have my model are just minimizing the
energy but we should really talk do this
I mean I'm just using your cluster I'm
just like throwing the atoms all in a
ball because if we do that we're gonna
have to start the thinking and who wants
to do it oh my god okay I know what the
bonds are actually if natural proteins
fall from a straight chain then you
shouldn't be able to denature them
because heating a dilute solution all
right I have an idea let's make it warm
you know let's fold but let's say the
temperature is 800 degrees is that gonna
make my protein flat
let's go look at how much energy it has
crazy amounts is that gonna make it flat
whoa
totally vibrating all over the place
it's denaturing it's denaturing
it's pretty one we're gonna go for more
steps 1 million steps
and here we need to fix it so I don't do
this don't they need to like think about
we're on putting moms and stuff and it's
hard
bonds are defined by the force field by
atom distance Pro all right let's go
look at the force field we have a force
field I know what that is now let's look
at the data the mass oh we can figure
out why they have stupid names
oh the atom tells me it's tight it's
looking at a type and then they tell me
the bond so that's a type 576 hydrogen I
say that's a nitrogen oh it's a nitrogen
tail
okay oh look it tells me the bond do we
know the lane okay okay I get what we're
doing here if we know the bond but then
I have to parse more shitty XML k -
what's a proper Forces let's see how my
denaturing proteins going I was just
killing my battery
hey guys you know it's easier than
folding proteins unfolding proteins
this is what happens when you boil a
protein I'm sure we could have picked a
realistic boiling temperature and not
eight hundred degrees Kelvin which is a
little unrealistic boiling and Kelvin
which isn't it just 373 I can't spell
boiling boiling 273 let's try a more
reasonable temperature of 373 can see if
it still boils well let that fold all
this one well look at how many steps
it's done Wow so many steps and get
folded yep you think I've folded
everything to my initial conditions are
too shady for default
dewfall gap
I must report that the protein did not
fall
did this one unfold at the much more
reasonable temperature of boiling he
doesn't unfold that much at boiling
okay guys alpha fold is stupid alpha
folds not a good way to solve this
problem I know about alpha fold I've
read the paper
the problem with alpha fold is twofold
one it's supervised learning they're
just learning to predict the sequences
based on the existing structure of
protons which is all well and good if
all you're trying to do is get a
slightly new protein but the truth is
any protein we can get the structure of
we can already study with actually
crystallography so it's not that useful
problem number two with alpha fault is
it still isn't that good while it does
better than the other things at that
competition the other things at that
competition are written by noobs and
they're basically just database searches
and copy pasting machines do a tear of
these fall solutions molecular dynamics
folding everything else this is top tier
this is like in Pikachu and Smash
Brothers 64 this is like the end being
being Marth and in smash brothers melee
this is like being the ice climbers
never because they suck
we need good in solution models
crystallography is the solid-state
Distortion yeah we need good in solution
models I agree which is like this is in
solution apparently apparently this
solvent is implicit bro that's
what I heard
okay we're boiling my protein it's kind
of boiling it's not turning into a
straight line I wanna say though
okay but we can't just place the atoms
randomly I understand are using
conjugate gradient I don't know you can
read my code I'm using the would change
does the Lang even interpreter there's a
language interpreter a good one I also
got rid of my non bonded method because
it was complaining yesterday Langevin
what about Matt Theo 8 what if I just
don't do that ok you guys telling me
that I actually have to write the code
to interpret the force field and Lane
was a Sigma Sigma Epsilon
no I'm not using conjugate gradient
minimization I'm not trying to minimize
the energy I'm trying to simulate the
dynamics so the protein will fall like
it does in nature I don't want to use
convex optimization we have to like no
angles and stuff okay how do I know what
bond class it is oh that's just like the
name of the atom so if like I have a c2
angles right and stuff there has to be
code that already does this already try
folding it absolute zero temperatures
I know exactly what its gonna do it
absolute zero I didn't study that who
wants to try the absolute zero
experiment can't believe you did this
experiment oh look it doesn't move at
all
well that's a cold protein look at that
cold it's moving why is it moving don't
this protein know about absolute zero
oh it's not really absolute zero what a
good molecular dynamics simulator you
see you can't actually make stop no you
guys you can't actually make stuff go to
absolute zero everyone knows this
because if you had something that was
actually absolute zero the Quantum's
would be upset because then you'd know
where it is so I don't know if this
simulator actually takes into account
quantum effect control and 95 thank you
for gifting subs to people appreciate it
have you tried denaturing by changing
the pH level I don't have to change the
pH I only want to change the temperature
cuz I found that because I put that in
my link Jabby an integrator I'm sorry
I'm sorry I don't know anything and then
I'm a bio script Kitty that's just what
I am one day I won't be a bio scripting
anymore though one day I
I don't see the default yeah I don't
understand do you really think that my
initial condition is the problem like I
don't think if I stretch it out it's
really gonna make a difference
to be fair I agree with you that it
comes out in nature mostly stretched out
just use amber tea leaf bro what's amber
tea leap Oh amber Tweep that's why amber
sleep
Oh
you can add hydrogen atoms to the
protein system using the H+ plus
web-surfer
small step size and more compute and
Hill please anything but that
my poor GPU is screaming already
methionine methionine check it out lamps
MD no I I'm fine with open mmm all I
want is something that's gonna
straighten out my protein not sure if it
matters like it seems like it Wiggles
around enough but I don't think it
matters
pull up both ends I mean yes I want to
pull it both ends can I do that
hey can I do that was it okay I have an
idea I know I don't don't I know the
protein is marking me wait I have an
idea about how to actually pull it both
acts straight down is an unrealistically
high energy starting place we added heat
to denature the protein yeah it all
looks like a bunch of tools cobble
together yeah to change the pH level you
just need to just simulate it folding as
it exits the ribosome yeah that's my
dream bro that's my dream all right who
wants to see what happens when I put the
temperature to 10,000 is that what we
want I don't think the force field was
designed for this oh yeah well that's
what happens I mean we could probably
straight now if we use like a
sufficiently strong electrical force
something happens you know okay this is
it a thousand kelvins
I mean it's definitely denatures well
straightens out pretty well those things
are still near each other
we're trying to simulate an atom by atom
how is the protein alive guys we are the
simulation right now add that to the
solvent I don't know how to add things
like that look at what it is
[Music]
this denaturing protein meal just means
to unfold
what does looks denatured protein I say
looks pretty denatured to me
what you think if I let it go now and I
put it back it'll refold but what if I
changed the temperature now that this is
done
I'm asked to edit out a bunch of thee
it's kind of renature
mm-hmm
looks somewhat hopeful
which we just pour more compute at it
and see what happens
all right we're done with that it's
never gonna fall right I mean let's just
look and make sure it didn't actually
fall
okay my longest compute yet did not hold
the protein so we loaded up the denature
protein we're gonna see if it renate
just now pour a lot of computing to it
wait does that work in real life
I don't know if that works in real life
do denature proteins stay denatured
radiation exceed okay reality protein
denaturation also
we can look in the papers and see how
they laid out their stuff initially it's
many cases denaturalization is
reversible
if it gets stuck at a local minimum
where I really can that can happen
I mean if this can't refold my protein I
don't I really don't think it's a
starting condition problem you know
the miss fold back up into a up
structure yeah I know if you boil an egg
I know this you know truth mm k1 is
reversible how to make them straight
very easily sounds really hard let's see
what the papers have to say
social interactions
please stand beta sheet peptide
thirty to five residues with unique 3d
art architecture all atom ones using
both Cindy and remedy
oh they used amber ff3 this is exciting
sure try amber ff3 who thinks that one
works
it's kind of like it wants to fall back
I think you're bad it's holding back
maybe not
why are you guys talking about damn
let's try a different force field let's
try from should we try from the denature
well I really like to scratch as it
moves all over the place
this forcefield seems more plausible too
because okay look the denatured one got
negative got negative that oh this is
getting similar okay I guess it's just a
different wow the denatured one actually
has lower energy okay maybe it doesn't
renature maybe I destroyed it
maybe my thousand Kelvin was too much
for it let's do my citation bro
protein does not fold by itself
I don't know how to do born I definitely
don't have a Barons dens dermis that the
time step was set to to femtoseconds
that's the same the coordinates were
saved every 10 picoseconds
[Music]
saving about the same so that's minus 50
people seconds simulations whoa into 15
minutes
and the total computer time required
WTF
whoa
that's fancy
let's see it's fully
just I like this force field better
doesn't it look better doesn't that look
more like it's gonna fold once I hooked
on itself this fall
hey look I want to be stretched out as
much as the next guy but I don't really
know how to do that it just looks like
it as less FPS do we want more FPS I can
get us more FPS guess all the FPS you
want yeah well they that was every 50 so
we're gonna just do right every that's
better not look us Morris yes this is
actually enough steps
I'm talking about DEFCON bro hacking is
dead
I mean hacking is live but like
organized hacking is dead
kind of like religion I didn't download
it but i up the FPS just so you guys
could see beautiful I never have to
download it says it so much more FPS but
oh no it's gonna make me run out of
space on my hard drive
do you like the more FPS oh it's
struggling well look at that it looks
like it's just like wrapped up on itself
and struggling look at its struggle that
does not look like it's gonna fold
anytime soon looks like it's crapoly
folded and struggling why do we do
anything bro oh look at it struggle oh
it's like oh I'm gonna fold but psych
not really
wait how much space is this gonna take
out well we're saving every 10
picoseconds and we're folding for five
milliseconds it's gonna be like
gigabytes do I have that many gigabytes
okay fine we'll put somewhere I have
lots of Jigga bites
I have 2.7 terabytes free on that hard
drive so you know oh look this one looks
less wrapped up on itself despite
setting the random seed the same it
seems like the random is actually
different well come on now that's does
look out look how unfolded that is
that's just begging to fault
okay so I think now we just have to wait
because we use the right forest field I
don't know should we maybe tomorrow
we'll watch the video of a fully folded
protein after this thing finishes which
will be done in 1.1 days according to my
map
and now it's begging to fold it's gonna
take five milliseconds upset hp-35 is
one of the most study proteins of the
field of protein folding
normal as controversy still exists
regarding the folding mechanism of this
protein if you have to fold its
structure you can use our SMD as a
metric to see if you're heading in the
right direction brow we could do that
but that's cheating
I mean oh no maybe we should do that
maybe that's what we'll do on can we
fold a villain protein part - perhaps
tomorrow
Oh big file now we did the hype train
today you missed that all right do we
have to Q&A tonight oh if we have QA for
the Camry folder protein the answer is
the answer to the Academy folder villain
protein is we will find out tomorrow
after this computes 41.1 days oh look
look at that deformation oh that's
beautiful
do we need more kudus set the problem I
have more Cudas does more Cudas make it
fold faster and tie up the FPS I know
what that does Oh fullscreen
I don't think my I oh it's it's a
hundred med file I really don't think my
macbook pro 16 inch can't load can I
slow it down I don't think it's folding
yet I think it's gonna take a day
I think folding card games is really
slow protein bro be folding I think
maybe all right let's uh if we have any
good questions we'll do Q&A if there's
good questions for today
otherwise that's today's stream thank
you all for watching I
bro-bro it might fold it's gonna take a
while I don't know how long it's gonna
take to fold these are the things we
don't know but the things that we do
know is that it's gonna take a day if it
does fold what if it hit something no no
no it's like writing a crypto
brute-force that you don't know if you
did it right except for the fact that
it's actually a lot we could do to know
if we did it right but we'll do that
tomorrow if we have to where did I learn
the biochemistry watch the last six
streams I did much money do I have in my
back can I have at least three dollars
it's getting like kind of tangled on
itself I think
let's let's uh as a closing graphic now
let's add liquorice perfect
where your bed in the kitchen can I
upload the Jupiter file
I'm not uploading the Jupiter file it's
too shitty to upload Jupiter stock stock
love but I did do the ball the folder is
uploaded and if you really want the
thing that views it it's just that to
add representations we just ngl view our
- licorice hyper ball
I want hyper balls contact that doesn't
look that cool hyper balls
where's the hyper balls
distance dot o hyper ball that just
looks like licorice
it looks cool in licorice for the type
of all but point my presentation o
ribbon is ribbon cool
I've already had rhythm rock it
surface whoa that one takes a long time
to render
seelix Orient lame
now this one's the best one
now fast forward to where you are the
movie hyperbole was kind of
disappointing
crowds are as GPUs don't seem to think
about crowdsourcing GPUs and I think we
could just try to fold more proteins I'm
not sure we can fold this protein faster
can I do D G dgse most of economics is a
scam
especially macroeconomics also the
business is the boom and bust cycle and
you just have to look at the s-curves
over there 50 years of salsa
they always all they always have these
ideas about like the cycles of business
and stuff um I don't like I don't
believe in any of them
does it look more folded now than it did
before
about the lunar cycle the lunar cycles
real well guys you know I just I just I
was looking at some of our charts and
graphs this morning and I'd like to
inform you guys that we're in a
recession as you can see the graph went
down economics have been predicting this
economists have been predicting this for
a long time now yet we knew it we knew
the recession was coming we just didn't
know when but you know overall markets
usually go up so that's pretty good
markets usually a good place to have
your your money you see some time we
have recessions but overall they look
very small this was a big one this was a
big a big bust
yeah but this one is a new recession
yeah we have a new recession here but
soon it'll be a green and recession will
be fixed yeah Jim you watch Mad Money
this morning I think that's pretty much
exactly what they said do I think this
Amber's no they're bullshitting people
or do they actually believe it I don't
know I think they don't really
understand what truth is so no I don't
think they actively think that they're
bullshitting people but I think that
they have like a poor understanding of
truth and by the way not all economics
is jocked
there is like a lot of sensible here you
want sensible economics um if you invest
in something that brings returns your
money goes up like for example if your
country and you invest in infrastructure
great investments if you're invest in
long term things great investment right
like it's it's there's economic truths
but they're like simple is supply and
demand
no no you gotta buy low and sell high
get in early buy the dip you know but no
but like economics and psychology who
watches CNBC what does this thing do oh
it loops the animation I get it oh this
is really lagging now look at that lag 2
FPS on that protein bro
no I don't watch Trump's daily news
update I heard it was an infomercial
oh the current models of deaths yeah
they're probably right she's a I did the
math at the end of it and I got 160,000
which is like right in the middle are
there other models I just assumed that
half of the city of Wuhan had been
infected or that extrapolate from there
and you got $160,000 you know we're
gonna watch this video and I think
that's gonna be the end of this dream
what do I think about dr. pouchy love
him or hate him I don't have a strong
opinion either way I'm sure he's doing
an acceptable political job but whatever
his position is you know that's how I
feel about politics in general do you
love Trump or hate Trump I mean I'm kind
of neutral you know here from all the
neutral people you know because all the
people who love somebody or hate
somebody you're posting online but a lot
of people are just kind of like neutral
is China passing USA is the world's
superpower
what's the GDP is the GDP real
you know they should hook me up with a
sponsor link for the chair if that's
true doesn't look very folded to me
looks kind of unfolded
no riots I mean if ten people riot the
media will tell us about how riots are
happening everywhere and you know will
we see a video of a riot in the next
month yes will there be widespread riots
but you'll be able to see yourself know
if it was a riot I participate I'm not
scared of coronavirus I wouldn't be like
oh no I might get infected
we're only Americans get free bunnies I
don't know where are you from you to get
any free money
who asked you got good for free money
but it's not free money the government
takes 40 percent of your money and then
gives you back 2 percent like honestly
imagine someone comes up to you in the
hallway is like bro give me your lunch
money and you give him 10 bucks and then
he hands you a dollar back and you're
like well thanks for the dollar no
nobody ever said that you don't get free
money no no email putin say hey have
some free money
[Music]
I mean I don't but do I feel burdened
County academies was a good opportunity
for me the do I think this is just
an opportunity no what's the political
saying never waste a good crisis and
whatever there's a crisis these folks
are always thinking about how they're
gonna profit do I think children should
go to schools
I don't think I'm their cure aging I'm
just trying to fold one throat would I
donate Tomba a 3d printer time to print
ventilator tubes if I thought I could
actually be useful I had be useful I
don't think anything come AI was 3d
printers print it would actually be very
useful I think the most useful thing we
can print this comma two's capitalism or
socialism what's the difference it's all
a spectrum right I'm not sure we to me
by capitalism socialism is capitalism I
don't know why people think socialism is
not capitalism for some reason
oh sweet we have double more movie to
watch I love torrenting this movie
I am just I started listen to the portal
my libertarian why do you think I'm a
libertarian he's a libertarian no I'm
not anything I have a wide variety of
opinions on many different things I
agree with libertarians on some things I
agree with conservatives on other things
and I view progressives and some other
things and I am an American that is
definitely true no I'm not a moderate
said I'm a mother and I have two very
extreme positions like that I'd like to
abolish intellectual property I don't
think any of that the Aryans are talking
about that should you give up on your
PhD yeah yo yeah by a sale chairman
I'm not debating anybody on IP you don't
do agree with me it's just like we're
not gonna win the way that you win the
IP battle is not and the way that you
win any battle right
it's an Andrew Breitbart quote actually
uh politics is downstream of culture oh
you don't win any of these battles in
the political arena you win them in the
cultural arena do I live on the fringe
of society what you mean in my in my
high-rise apartment building in San
Diego with my 16 inch MacBook Pro my
iPhone 11th row with three cameras you
know we're hearing $200 hoodies do I
look like I live on the fringes of
society
Alex bought it from you remember Alex
elephant already on the cloud
best country other than the US I like as
far as countries I feel that I could
actually like live in and integrate
pretty well with the population I like
the UK
I like the Netherlands as far as
countries where I could live for a while
I like Japan like Malaysia yeah those
ones probably I'm Australian citizen
like Australia I mean I'm sure you've
looked at probably New Zealand as well
my only experience with Switzerland is
that it was really expensive thanks for
the bed Sam on the fringe problem the
fringes of society you have with the
groceries away I had a girl come over I
have to clean the apartment she judged
me if I'd groceries out yeah the hoodie
sweats a lot if I like Florida doll it's
probably true when you do a podcast once
every two weeks
oh if you book guests from me aren't
doing that GG thank you for subscribing
thank you whoa we got a hype train going
do I ever use clout to get girls I don't
think it works yeah you know yo level
one I train we're talking about a girl
coming over is it always a new girl
no no just like a rotation do I think
Corona deaths really matter there's an
interesting thing about how like CDC
numbers show that deaths are down by by
10,000
no rotation sounds that's that's you
know what I mean
everybody everybody does this these days
no like honestly ever since you could
get girls on the internet there's plenty
of girls on the internet now it's great
if I had to like go to bars and meet
girls like Abed the would be hard
oh no maybe not they just got to
practice at it what do we think we'll
reach the apex of the curve Oh like two
weeks you can look they're already
flattening out okay for these girls
friends of mine where are their girls on
the Internet if there's an ad probably
not you know it was a lot of girls
Instagram why do you think I cared about
my Instagram followers but it would be
nice to have a blue checkmark you know
is that what you'd be my cloud not only
is cloud I mean I'm saying like you know
you tell you tell girls like oh man I
was sued by Sony for hacking the
PlayStation that doesn't really work
that well thank you for subscribing know
if it's gonna fall bros I think it's
gonna take a day staff in the child
whose staff
I always think they're coming for me
staff
I like the affection the best pick-up
line or pickup lines even real
it's the feds at which you're always
watching out for the feds what if it
fails to fold then my three hours of
time will be in vain and I'll feel like
a failure give you 300 bits thank you
hide the mediocrity boy staff is here oh
I like that I like that you know can we
get the hi tank we keep it going we got
two minutes with 39%
we'll keep the stream going as long as
the hype train keeps going do I know
June go mom no Alex good friend of mine
really like how she bought me Eddie
Brian Cantrell no I feel like I have
heard that name before
dude video game Smash Bros 64
what have I regretted most of the past
five years I mean I why I said starting
a company I would really advise
everybody not to start a company I want
to go on speaking tours and be like an
auntie motivational speaker but I don't
know I'm not really sure we also would
have done but maybe I just say this not
because it's profitable but it wasn't
profitable I really regretted doing it
staff is here subscribe sweet
why would I advise against it yeah
[Music]
there's a lot of downside with not that
much upside everything's kind of your
fault and you have to deal with
everything it's it's just it's a
responsibility and a burden you know
that's the beauty of being a start-up
employee versus yeah there's the start
in the company is when your startup
employee you know you can quit and the
company will continue on it's harder
well yeah the potential payoff is
tremendous but sweet yeah it's like
owning a home yeah and I wouldn't really
want home ownership I don't want to have
children so yeah I really if you have
another option don't start a company so
yeah I would say that's I don't know oh
let's say like what's my biggest regret
I don't know if they really regretted
like I did what I did and that's like my
life right maybe it's Stockholm Syndrome
I'm glad you like to primont delights ah
you wouldn't choose the end well think
about the end a bit more I took at the
end I interpret the end when I first
read it I took the end very literally
and then I thought about it as I got
older and I realized what the end really
was
you know write the questions are getting
worse he's having problem so I'm going
to like to learn to allow that anything
to be real long it's kind of what I
think I've watched VR porn yeah I wasn't
that impressed
I'm an avid shear who's am a shear OC
your twitch chat i started vr porn no no
one gets it half that that's and look up
Jude Camila what will be the benefit for
channel subscribers when I take over the
world
Jagger artist of your home you better
subscribers do you want Kazakh Stan you
want to rule Kazakhstan I'll give you
Cossacks
I just imagine like gross
pharmaceuticals trying to interact with
the ethereum blockchain everyone's
really hyped on this aetherium 2.0 I
don't know
I'm still trying to do proof of steak I
think through the steaks pretty dumb mad
complex no metallic is also genius
shard and stuff makes sense
oh just about sharding yeah I probably
pretty good know if you could get a
theorem if you could build an aetherium
computer that scales better that gives
you like a thousand x to compute I think
that could be a lot of these cases my
pals next more computer also mean like a
thousand X cheaper a thousand X faster
you're really shilling for Carnell
thousand X less decentralized oh yeah
you gotta make trade-offs an engineer is
all about trade-offs maybe a theory was
a little too decentralized already proof
of stake is finished no proof state
doesn't work every proof of stake thing
I've ever seen
turns into like more and more complexity
being tacked on to fix problems and then
they think that they fixed all the
problems but like there's more because
there's so much complexity but just
nobody can find them anymore dow broke
it there and I looked at that word with
Darien I mean I wouldn't have hard for
it but that's just me all right all
right good stream that's the stream
that's the questions tomorrow we're
gonna find out if the protein folds
thank you all for joining thank you for
being on the stream with me I really
appreciate you all except I appreciate
the subscribers more so if you're not a
subscriber make sure to hit that
subscribe button if you don't follow
with the notifications make sure the
notification button wherever it is on
your computer if it's over here or if
it's over here I'm chilling for groans
tomorrow we find out does the protein
fold everybody in your prayers if you'd
like to ask
you get through all the things that you
usually pray for like love and peace and
the end of coronavirus maybe at the end
you Democrat the protein Falls a little
bit till I like that that's always just
joking for instance it's my mockery of
youtubers I honestly I don't really care
I don't really care if you subscribe or
you took the notification button I do
these dreams mostly because it's just
people to hang out with and talk to and
like I get something I get a link to
some good stuff what time tomorrow
no yeah figure it out
I could night everybody if I made
mistakes please file issues on corona
thank you